# **Kun Tian**

25 River Dr S, Apt 903, Jersey City, NJ 07310 • (443)824-3257 • kuntian0214@gmail.com

#### **Profile**

Kun Tian graduated from Master of Science in Finance program from the Johns Hopkins University. She has strong logic thinking demonstrated through past working experience and case studies. She is also proficient in financial analysis developed through building models using MS Excel and MATLAB. She is interested in future internship/full-time job opportunity in the related areas of asset management and trading in North America and Asia.

#### Education

### Master of Science, Finance, Johns Hopkins University

Aug 2014

Relevant Coursework: Financial Modeling, Advanced Hedge Fund Strategy, Fixed Income, Derivatives, etc.

GPA: 3.24

## Bachelor of Accounting, Capital University of Economics and Business

Jul 2012

Relevant Coursework: Financial Accounting, Corporate Finance, Advanced Accounting, Taxation, etc.

GPA: 3.65 GMAT: 690

#### **Exchange Student Program, Boston University**

Aug 2011-Dec 2011

Finance Courses: Investment Analysis and Portfolio Management, Personal Finance, Financial Management

GPA: 3.74

## Program Experience

#### Vice President of Education, Johns Hopkins Equity Research Team

Oct 2013-Aug 2014

Johns Hopkins University Carey Business School, Washington D.C. Metro Area

- · Conducted conference calls, industry analysis and equity research on various stocks and firms
- Trained on fundamental, quantitative and technical equity analysis under the instruction of experienced professional
- · Prepared equity research reports and deepen the knowledge about related industries and reinforced equity analysis skills

### Team Leader, Hedge Fund Trading Strategy Project

Jun 2014-Aug 2014

Johns Hopkins University Carey Business School, Baltimore, Maryland Area

- · Used statistic arbitrage to modify and execute trading strategies on equity market
- · Conducted screening process on US and emerging markets by selected criteria
- · Evaluated performance and risk of different strategies and implemented them with dynamic high-frequency trading features

#### Professional Experience

#### Financial Analyst, Finance and Accounting Department

Jul 2012-Apr 2013

Novartis Pharma Co. Ltd. Beijing

- Calculated and distributed revenue deduction for hospitals and distributors: bidding compensation, cash discount, price-cut
  compensation, etc.
- · Supported price matrix calculations using excel functions and macros
- Transferred old data to new data system and make sure it ran correctly
- · Supported revenue deduction reporting and maintained documentation per internal control requirements
- Improved the customer (internal/external) satisfaction rates for actual revenue deduction in communication and reconciliation process.

## Intern, Internal Auditor, Finance Bureau

Apr 2012-Jun 2012

Ministry of Commerce, People's Republic of China

- · Managed bidding process: selected accounting firms and ensured that all the bidding procedures were fair and legal
- Participated in the subordinate organization society leaders economic responsibility auditing, and participate in auditing and tracking process of project using fiscal funds
- Collaborated with National Audit Officers in their auditing program in Ministry of Commerce to develop strong relationships between national auditors and officers in Ministry of Commerce in order to make auditing process going smoothly

## Intern, Auditing Department

Feb 2012-Mar 2012

Deloitte, Beijing

- · Implemented annual audit for China Railway Group and handled multiple tasks
- · Successfully maintained a good relationship with client personnel
- · Participated in the cash and bank section and provided support for other colleagues, e.g. documentations, cast, review audit report

## Additional Information

**Skills:** accounting, financial modeling, portfolio management, hedging, risk management **Computer Skills:** MATLAB, MS Office, Access, SAP, Bloomberg Data System

Languages: Chinese: Mandarin (First language); English: TOEFL (106 out of 120)